Master.
I'm looking at the amulet.
You are so amazing, Master.
With just a simple amulet,
you can turn an ordinary bow
into a divine weapon.
It's not a divine weapon.
It's an enchanted weapon.
When the magic power is exhausted,
the bow will return to normal.
Although you don't have much magic power,
your spiritual energy is not bad.
If you practice,
even without enchantment,
you can master some spells.
Master, do you mean
you are willing to teach me?
Although you are usually noisy,
you have a pure nature.
You have some affinity for cultivation.
If you really want to learn,
I can teach you.
Thank you, Master.
Rise.
I don't know when Tu Luohua will arrive.
Let me teach you how to practice magic first.
Thank you, Master.
Fufu, go find some arrows.
Go find some arrows.
Right away.
Miss Gesang.
Don't be nervous.
Let's chat.
Lord Hu.
Talk about what?
Miss Gesang, you are
a tree demon.
What?
Are you going to kill me?
Though you are a demon,
you have no hostility in you.
This means you've never killed anyone.
So I won't do anything to you.
No need to be so nervous around me.
Then what do you want from me?
I just want to tell you
not to have any wicked thoughts about Zuzong.
If you make a mistake in the future,
I will definitely not spare you.
I only thought since he was a Golden Immortal,
he must be different from ordinary mortals.
I just wanted him to transfer his divine power to me.
I would accept anyone, whether a pig or a dog.
I didn't even take a good look at his face.
Looking at him now,
even without an immortal body,
his upright posture
and refined demeanor
make him a supreme beauty in this world.
Sneaking around.
Brother Qingxuan.
I saw you standing here so tall and graceful,
alone in the empty corridor,
so I was afraid to disturb you.
Look,
the spring scenery filling the garden
is quite beautiful.
Every flower, every blade of grass,
every terrace, every scene,
are all illusions.
It's not bad to have someone accompanying you
in this bubble of an illusion.
Golden Immortal,
are you from the heavens?
It depends on how you understand
the heavens.
My mother told me
that I am also a spirit branch that fell from the heavens.
Which heaven did you fall from?
How would I know?
It's just that,
as a tree,
you know,
we take root and sprout wherever we fall.
I am just one of thousands.
You are different from them.
Of course.
I'm so unique.
They have so many children,
some were cut down to be made into roof beams,
some were so dull
that they are still a piece of broken wood after a hundred years.
Only I have the highest cultivation level.
Indeed.
You are not that young.
You should have cultivated for over a thousand years,
or perhaps...
Golden Immortal,
my age...
But you look very young,
about fifteen or sixteen.
If you don't tell,
no one will know your real age.
I didn't expect Brother Qingxuan with the eternal icy face
to be such a kind person.
Handsome,
sweet-talking and kind-hearted.
Girls must all like you.
This damn man is invulnerable,
impervious to everything,
stubborn and unyielding.
Master, Master, Master.
Hey.
Why panic?
Is there anything else?
What could I have?
If you don't,
I do.
Hurry up and go.
Your power is weak,
and you don't know any spells.
If you encounter monsters in the future,
just shout at this,
"Sister, save me."
And I will come.
Okay. Thank you.
Gesang,
you must also be careful.
If you're in danger, just call for
Master.
Just take care of yourself, rookie.
Master,
it's my first day of training.
I'm still a bit nervous,
but I'll do my best.
Give me your hand.
You're going to hit me before we even start?
It's for you.
For me?
You have a mortal body
with no cultivation.
This ring can serve as a medium
to help you draw spiritual energy into your body.
You have an excellent innate bone structure.
If you temper it with spiritual energy
and cultivate diligently,
your future achievements
will be limitless.
Thank you, Master, for not despising my mortal dullness.
Put it on.
Master, I got it.
I will definitely work harder in the future.
This ring
can only help you absorb spiritual energy.
You have a unique physique.
Converting spiritual energy into magic power
shouldn't be difficult for you.
Practice more in the future.
Never forget your original intention.
Yes.
Immortal!
Is everything ready?
To answer the Immortal,
everything is ready in the main hall.
Qiang Haihui.
Jie Qianghaihui.
Ping Jieqiang.